[Music]
cuz only a
Sho will rain
forever to his kingdom there'll be no
end truly there are
names there are
ti there are Ag and tals of
strength but only as you are will R
forever to his kingom there will be no
only yesu only
yes will re
forever to his kingom there be no can we
lift up our hands and thank the King of
Kings he's called the king of glory I
don't know how you want to tell him
thank you tonight but please tell him
thank you there are things that men can
do but there are some things only God
can
[Music]
do thank you go ahead and thank him
thank him for your life Zaria thank him
UK thank
him us thank him Canada thank him
coinonia Global thank
[Music]
him thank him for doing what only God
can do Nicodemus came and said Rabbi we
know that thou art a teacher sent from
God for no man can do these Miracles
except God be with him
him are you saying thank you thank him
for your life thank him for his hand
upon your life do not take his
faithfulness for
granted take a minute to say thank you
it's part of the service it's part of
the coia experience we are grateful
people we
magnify your
name we
glorify your
magnify your name yes Lord we
name we
magnify your name for everything you
have done we
glorify your
name we magnify
your
name and we
glorify your name for the Miracles for
your Mighty hand in our
mid give him thanks for healings for
restoration for the power of your word
in our
midst we
magnify your
name we
glorify your
[Music]
name now the nation
see
Jesus lifted
up you are
exalted now the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
glorify bre Lord bre breath Lord breath
breath upon my life
I receive I receive I manifest
manifest your power your power your
wisdom your wisdom Nation Nation see
Jesus see Jesus Lift It Up Lift It Up
you are
exalted I receive I receive I manifest I
manifest your power your power your
wisdom your wisdom the Nations the na
see Jesus Jesus Lift It Up Lift It Up
glorified
GL I will not forget long
your
benefits I will not forget
Lord your
benefits I will never forget
faithfulness how can I forget
Lord your
benefits I will not forget Lord
your
benefits I will never forget
Lord your
benefits I will not forget
benefits let me not forget
Lord your
[Music]
benefits I will never forget
Lord your
Ben my glory the lifter up of my
head you're my
glory the lifter up of my
hand you are my glory the lifter up of
my hand
remain my glory the lifter up of my
[Music]
hand you are my glory the lifter up of
my
[Music]
head I think this is a good place to
sing that song get the mic come
[Music]
H
King chist
[Music]
sing one more
time my
command
yes
you you're ready my
king my
king
oh
oh oh
w
[Applause]
we give you
worship
worship the highest praise to the king
we give you
worship worship
the deepest praise to the
king
to we give you the
highest highest to the K we give you the
loudest I pra to the king we lift up
holy
hands I
pra you have taken all my
shame you have taken all the
weakness you have taken all
limitations you have taken all the
sorrow you have taken away
disappointment you've taken away my
cheer
you have made them
yours
to we give you we give you we give you
the highest praise we give you we give
you keep
praying you the highest
prise highest we give you we give you
give
you we give you we give you we give
you we give you we give
you we give you
worship
worship the highest praise to the king
we give you
worship worship the
praise to the
[Music]
king
restore everything that was lost
restore everything that was stolen
[Music]
restore you will
restore
restore everything that was lost
restore everything that was stolen
restored
everything that was lost
restore you will restore one more
time
restore everything that was lost
Resto everything that was stolen
everything that was stolen
Resto everything everything that was
lost rest Resto
you will you
Resto
restore everything that was lost
restored everything that was stolen
[Music]
restore the honor that was lost
restored you will
restore
restore everything that was lost
restore my
God everything that was stolen
restore everything that was lost
restore you will
Resto
[Music]
to
you will
[Music]
the
l
a
[Music]
is the
kingom in
the is the
power is the glory
Forever sing
yours is the
kingom yours
is the
power your is's the glory
forever one more
time the
power is the
glory
forever yesu
yesu
God our
Salvation Mighty in the midst of his
people
tonight just the
voices Yeshua
yes go ahead and
worship
yes
I have searched and searched all the
Earth searched and searched all the
Earth and found
that I have searched and searched all
the Earth searched and searched all the
Earth and I
found oh there's no one like
you
you are
yesu there's no one like
you no one none comes
close
[Applause]
yes
oh for the last time now
together
[Applause]
yes I
receive I
manifest your
power and your we
till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up you are
exalted I
receive I
manifest your
power your
wisdom to the
Nations see
Jesus lifted up
glorified oh my life you have been
faithful sing it for
me oh my life you have been
so every bread that I am
a I will
sing of the
goodness of God
one more
[Music]
time my
you yes you have been
my oh my life you have been so so good
every
breath every breath that I
am I will
sing I will sing of the good of the
goodness
God hallelujah no wall you would kick
out lie you w tear down coming after me
no Shadow you will light up no Shadow
you will light up Mountain you w CL up
coming after
me no more you won kick down Li w't tear
down up to me
I love you
forever I love you
forever
Lord I love you
forever I love you
forever Lord one more time I love you I
love you forever I love love you
forever I love you
forever
Lord hallelujah let your
power holy ghost
power rest on
me rest on
me let your power holy ghost power rest
on
me rest on
me
oh oh rest on
oh rest on
me
oh rest on me the holy ghost power rest
on
me Let Your Grace this Grace called
favor rest on
me rest on me Let Your
Grace sh
rest on
me rest on
me rest on me
oh rest on me
oh rest on me his on
fav rest on me BL your power your power
the power to
prosper rest on me
rest on me let your power power to
prosper rest on
me rest on
me me the power to
rer rest on me
let your power power to
prosper rest on
me rest on
me let your power power to
prosper rest on
me rest on
me
oh rest on
me oh oh rest on me the power to
prosper rest on
me let your power power to
prosper rest on me rest on me let your
spirit Spirit of wisdom rest on me rest
on
me
oh rest on me oh
oh rest on
me
oh rest on me Spirit of wisdom rest on
me I'm under the shadow of your
wings your influence is all over
me I am under the shadow of your
me I am under the shadow of
your your influence is all over
me
yeah
I am
victorious I have
overcome I am
overcome s I am
victorious I am over
come I am
victorious Hallelujah
he who was the
son has eternal
life he who has the
life I have the
son so I have eternal
life he who has the
son
ET go ahead and pray holy
holy
holy holy
is the
Lord God
Almighty is the
Almighty my life is full of your
glory my life is full of your glory keep
praying and the people say oh holy
holy
holy holy
sh holy
holy
holy I've made up my mind to go God's
way for the rest of my life
I've made up my
mind
oh my
lifting Has
Come
Oh My
lifting has
come
oh
my
Rising Has
Come
Oh My
Rising Has
Come
Oh My
lifting Has
Come
Oh My LIF
has
come how be here
worshiping all of the days of my life
how be here
how be here helping
you all of the days of my life I'll be
here helping
you all of the days of my
life I'll be here holding
life how
be holding
you all of the days of my life but I
lose look to
yahe
Yahweh My Hope Is
yahe I Look To
yahe
Forever
yah yahe one more time we look to yahe
to yah
yah our hope is
yahe yah
way we look to
yahe
yahe Forever
Yahweh
yeh oh
oh oh oh
yah oh
oh you're on your way to better
days pray something is changing you're
on your way to Better Days
you're on your way to
Paradise never weak again ah you're on
your way to better days it's God's
prophecy for your life you're on your
way to better
days status is
changing there no more
decline you're on your way to
P stus is
changing no more
decline you're on your way to better
day you're on your
way on your
way to better
days you're on your way
on your
way go who is this king of
glory the lord strong and mighty the
Lord Mighty in battle
amen who is this king of glory the lord
strong and mighty
might for thine
is the power and the glory
forever and ever
amen the power and the glory
forever amen
amen
amen amen to your lifting and your
Rising
amen
amen to the change of season
Lord you took my pain away and then you
gave me joy you're my peace my melody in
the center of the
storm you gave me a brand new song to
sing to you that's why I will lift up my
voice and
sing yeah yeah
yeah you've taken the pain and the
sorrow away you've given me peace and
deniable there's no need to cry cuz
you're always with me you're my father
my
everything
yeah
[Music]
just breathe your name upon me
breathe just breathe your name upon me
breathe keep coming come to
Jesus your name breathe Lord please keep
standing stand you don't have to
kneel just breathe your name upon me
Bree
come just breathe your name upon me Brea
he can give you a new beginning
tonight is your
name
I'm chasing after you no matter what I
have to do cuz I need you more and
more I'm chasing after you no matter
what I have to
do I need you more and
more
for the way of the Lord is the way of
wiom I choose the way of the
Lord for the way of the Lord is the way
of
wisdom I choose the way of the Lord for
the way of of the Lord is the way of
wisdom I choose the way of the Lord now
breathe Lord breathe breathe Lord
breathe breathe upon my
life breathe Lord breathe breathe Lord
breath breath upon my life
I
receive I
manifest your
power and your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lift it
up
[Music]
ex who is like you Lord in all the
Earth much less love and beauty and less
worth listen nothing in this world can
[Music]
satisfy Jesus you're the god that gr run
dry Treasure of my heart and of my
soul in my weakness you are merciful
Redeemer of my past and present
wrongs you're the holder of my future
days to
come you're
presence
is to
me your PR
I glory be to
[Music]
God glory be to
God glory be God you call me now
call
me
call I am
victorious
I have
overcome I am
victorious I have
victorious I am
over I am the
glorious and I have
overcome taken the pain and the sorrow
away you've given me peace
undeniable there no need to cry cuz
you're always with me you're my father
my
every oh man
my sing
it Lord you took my pain away and then
you gave me joy you're my peace my
melody in the center of the storm you
gave me a brand new to sing to you
that's why I will lift up my voice and
sing
[Music]
y glory be to
God I
glory be to
God glory be to
God
pra glory be to God
hallelujah
hallelujah glory be to God
hallelujah Glory
[Applause]
God glory be to
God glory glory be to
God
glory one more
time glory glory be to
God glory be to
[Music]
God glory be
God yeah yeah glory be to
God I
receive I
manifest your
power and your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
exal I
receive I manifest
your
power and your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
glorified glory be to
God glory be to God
glory be to
God glory be to
God glory be
[Music]
God glory be to God
hallelujah
hallelujah Glory be to God
hallelujah glory be to God
hallelujah hallelujah glory glory be to
[Applause]
God glory be to
God
glory H
hallelujah hallelujah
glory be to God
hallelujah
hallelujah GL glory be to
God hear
me hear me in the name of
Jesus father what Chariot should I be
joining in this
[Music]
season what Partnerships do I need in
this season to break out of and to
become part of
who is an ally indeed in this season it
will not come by physical appearance you
will need the ability to
see what should I be studying and
meditating upon right now what business
will produce the next wealthy people in
the next 5 years don't assume the seen
eye is the
solution GL be to
God glory be to
[Music]
God
knes KN be
hey
in the in
the in the in
the say in the in
the
listen
hey
[Music]
oh when the glory
comes there'll be no words to say
when the glory
comes there'll be no words to
say
oh sing it one time when the glory comes
when the glory
comes there'll be no words to
say oh
oh when the glory comes when the glory
comes there'll be no words to
say when the glory
say
oh when the glory comes when the
glor there be no to
say
the glory be to
God just
listen glory be to
God glory be to God
[Music]
glory be to
God glory be to God
Hallelujah
hallelu
Hallelujah Glory be to
God glory be to
God in another
measure sing it for
[Applause]
me another measure another measure
upon your life upon your
ministry Holy Ghost another
1 receive it in the name of Jesus I
impart that Grace upon you in the name
of
Jesus
meure Holy Ghost another
1,000 listen another another
1,000 another 1,000 measure 1,000 cubits
in the name of Jesus 1 another
1,000 1, another
1,000 another 1, another 1,00
[Music]
tonight
listen
[Music]
it's a prophetic word help them please
this is part of my teaching oh ladies
and gentlemen have returned back this is
my
assignment y means it is over Yak means
it it is finished when Jesus hung upon
the cross he said it is finished take it
high for me please in the name of Jesus
you came to church it's it's a song that
God put in my spirit it's not a special
number I'm speaking to your spirit
man no matter the
[Music]
over delay over disappointment over rise
and fall over in the name of Jesus
Christ
[Music]
it's
over surely there is an end dear man of
God
[Music]
businessman listen you see an
Apostolic and and a prophetic
Ministry is a deeply spiritual Ministry
that operates very strongly by the gift
of
discernment let me tell you if this is
all the service today and we suspend the
teaching and do this it is still a
successful service are we together
now for some of you this night you go
back home to sleep you will hear this
song again it doesn't matter whether you
can speak out or not but this time
around you will not be the one singing
it you will hear it from the boils of
your
spirit surely there is an end surely
there is an end oh someone hear me it
looks like Ministry is not opening up
surely there is an end everything that
has a beginning has an
end
that sickness will not kill you I assure
you cancer has an end HIV has an end
fire has an end disappointment has an
end
y
in your
life the negative
[Music]
Seasons
Hallelujah please play the strings for
me see the Bible
says do not be drunk with wine wearing
is excess is says but be ye filled with
the spirit and among the many signs that
you are full of the spirit is that you
will begin to speak to yourself in
Psalms and hymns and spiritual songs
spiritual songs are not special numbers
you must know how to align your spirit
there are times that God will give you a
song that song carries an anointing once
the anointing comes on you the song
Fades you will not even remember it
again that song was not a special number
it was a ladder to Usher you into a
realm please don't be distracted God is
doing something tonight for some of you
God is responding to the prayer you
prayed yesterday the prayer you prayed
last week some of you you have been on
fasting and prayers asking questions God
said go to church he said when I came to
the house of God then understood
I
we're going to sing this song One More
Time whether you can sing it or not you
just listen it's not a special number
it's a prophetic decree to the heavens
oh it has come to end When God says it
is over it means it is over When God
says it is over it means it is over you
will sing it over your finances you will
sing it over your health
condition listen he said said I will
call upon the Lord who is worthy of
Praise so shall I be saved from my
enemies there are songs in the spirit
God songs of
Deliverance are you
ready
yeah
in your life in your finances in your
home
in your ministry the end of Oppression
has come to an
end
more
yes
we
car
yes it matters who is
speaking Jesus is more than a
prophet the owner of the heavens and the
earth when he speaks it is final when he
says you are lifted you are lifted when
he says you are blessed you are
[Music]
blessed in your
life
[Music]
y
car for a barren woman this is your
[Music]
song It's Over
over that
unemployment
listen God is called
Alpha and he's called Omega the Bible
calls him the beginning it also calls
him the end
breathe Lord breathe breathe Lord
breathe breath upon my
life breathe Lord breathe breathe Lord
breathe breathe upon my life very simple
song says breath Lord Brea breath Lord
breath breath upon my life now listen I
receive I
manifest your
power and your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
exalted I receive
I
manifest your
power your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
glorify say breath Lord breath Lord Bre
Bre Lord Bre Bre upon my life
Bre Bre Lord bre Lord bre Lord Bre Bre
upon my life very simple song say breath
breath Lord breath breath Lord Brea bre
upon my
life I
receive I
manifest your power
and your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
exalted say exalted exalted exalted
exalted exalted exed exalted exalted
he's exalted exalted exalted exalted
exalted exalted exalted
exalted Lord breath breathe Lord breathe
breathe upon my life is a Prayer Will
you breathe Lord breathe breath Lord
breath breath upon my
life I receive
I
manifest your
power and your
wisom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
exalted I
receive I
manifest your power your
power and your WI
the nation Jes see Jesus Lift It Up Lift
It
Up
glorify Brea Lord say bre Lord Brea Brea
bre Lord Brea breath upon my life sing
breath lord lord lord lord lord
upon my one more time say bre lord lord
lord
lord fre upon my
life you're exalted exalted exalted
exalted exalted exalted
exalted Lift It Up Lift It Up Lift It Up
Lift It Up
lifted Up Lift It Up lifted Up Lift It
Up exalted exalted exalted exalted
exalted exalted
exalted I receive I receive I
manifest manifest your
power your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
exalted breathe Lord breathe breathe
Lord breathe breathe upon my life that's
your prayer now breath Lord breath
breath
[Music]
Lord sing breath Lord Brea Lord Brea
Lord breath Lord breath breath upon my
life turn it into a prayer
tonight Lord Bre Bre
Lord upon my
life Jesus breing Lord breath breath
Lord breath breath upon my
life I
receive I
manifest your
power and your
wisdom till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
exalted till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
glorified till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
glorified till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted up one last time
now say bre Lord bre Lord bre
bre Lord Bre Bre upon my life say bre
Lord
Lord You're exalted exed exalted ex
lifted Up Lift It Up exalted exalted
exalted
exalted exalted exalted exalted exed
exalted now I stretch my hands in the
name that is above all
names there are men and women who will
drink of this Fountain right now I
decree and declare I want you to pick
them and bring them out very quickly
father you gave me this song by the
spirit and you said upon singing it the
spirit of wisdom and power will rest
upon many for their Destinies therefore
I stretch my hands at the count of three
may this Fountain break open 1 2 3 take
that Grace now take that Grace now bring
them out take that Grace now take that
Grace
now bre
lord
lord lord Brea bre upon my life say bre
lord lord lord bre Lord
bre
upon one more time say bre
lord lord breing lord breing breing upon
my I receive I receive I manifest I
manifest your power
your
wisdom the
nation
Jesus lift it
up exalt exalt I receive I receive I
manifest I
manifest your power your power your
wisdom W the nation the nation see
jesuses Jesus Lift It Up Lift It Up
glorify
glorify Lord Lord Bre Bre Lord Bre Bre
upon my life say breing lord lord breing
lord lording
lord till the
Nations
see
Jesus lifted
up
exalted till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
glorified till the Nations bring them
out see
Jesus lifted
up
exalted till the
Nations see
Jesus lifted
up
glorify breath Lord breath breath Lord
breath upon my
heart
[Music]
is